https://www.fatiguesarmynavy.com/privacy-statement/

Loading... Please wait...
Our Privacy Policy
Fatigues Army Navy is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We sometimes collect personal information from our users. This Web page explains what information we collect, why we collect it, what we do with it and what you can do about it.Collection of Personal InformationFatigues maintains the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information that we obtain from our users. We do not disclose personal information to any party except to our credit card company for the purpose of conducting sales transactions. We never sell users' email addresses, personal information or IP addresses.Our site uses order forms and registration forms for users to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like users' email addresses, names, telephone numbers and mailing addresses) and financial information (like account or credit card numbers) through these forms. Contact information from the forms is used to send orders to our customers, to send information about our products and services and for the purposes of record keeping. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Stop Receiving Mail section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.We sometimes contact by telephone users who have ordered products or services from us with information regarding their order.About IP AddressesFatigues may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to prevent credit card fraud. Fatigues will never report these IP addresses to a third party. An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve" up Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When guests request pages from Fatigues, our servers may log the users' IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us.Use of CookiesCookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard; you'll find them at most major Web sites. Fatigues sometimes uses cookies to track certain information for our users' convenience.Links to Other SitesYou should be aware that when you are on FatiguesArmyNavy.Com you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from our site that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up on the Web.SecurityThe importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our users is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of our users' financial information from their computers to our servers, utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to our users' information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.How to Stop Receiving Mail from UsIf you do not want to receive e-mail or occasional mailings from us, you can let us know by sending us email at customerservice@fatiguesarmynavy.com or by calling our number 1-877-612-1253.Correct or Update InformationIf you would like to correct or update information that you have previously provided us with, you can let us know by sending us email at customerservice@fatiguesarmynavy.com, calling our number 1-877-612-1253 or you can send mail to the following postal address: Fatigues Army Navy Rt 6 PO Box 470, Hawley, Pa 18428.Your Acceptance of These TermsBy using this site, you signify your assent to the Fatigues Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. You can send e-mail to us with any further questions.Contacting UsIf you have any questions our privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
Fatigues Army Navy Customer ServiceRt 6 PO Box 470Hawley, Pa 18428customerservice@fatiguesarmynavy.com1-877-612-1253
Pages
Home
Sales & Specials
Featured Items
About Us
Contact
Customer Testimonials
Fatigues' Blog
Popular Brands
Rothco Fox Outdoor Products Fatigues Army Navy Gear Company Smith & Wesson Alpha Industries Ontario Knife Company Kiwi Shoe Products Zippo Ka-Bar AO American Optical Eyewear
View all brands
News
The Soft Shell Tactical Jacket Collection
These Soft Shell Tactical Jackets are the ultimate in design, constructed with …
The Colors Of Spring Women’s Paratrooper Fatigues
The Women's Paratrooper Colored Camo Fatigue Pants are made with a comfortable …
Big Spring Sale Savings
Big Spring Sale Savings15% Off Site WideCoupon Code: Thaw Also FREE …
